Guide to the The Review of Contemporary Fiction/Dalkey Archive Press: records, 1980-1990
Department of Special Collections
- Series I: Review of Contemporary Fiction
  - Schmidt
    - A Gallery of Women in Carlos Fuentes' Song of the Blind -George Gordon Wing (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fuentes on Mexican Feminophobia - M.E. de Valdes (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Carlos Fuentes: Dreaming of History - William Kennedy (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Distant Relations: A Conjunction of Opposites -Guy Davenport (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Gringo viejo/The Old Gringo: 'The Rest Is Fiction -Jonathan Tittler (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - "Magic Realism and Fantastic History: Carlos Fuentes' Terra Nostra and Giambattista Vico's The New Science -Lois Parkinson Zamora (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Provisional Historicity: Reading through Terra Nostra -Carl Gutierrez (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Esch Is Luther - Milan Kundera (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Desire and Paqer, Love and Revolution: Carlos Fuentes and Milan Kundera - Wendy B. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Christopher Unborn: Rage and Laughter - Julio Ortega (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - "Metamorphosis in Fuentes 'Aura' - Olsen (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - After the Nouveau Roman: Bare New Names in French Fiction -Renee A. Kingcaid (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - The Generation of Spanish Novelists after Franco -John C. Ackers (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Book Reviews (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Books Received (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Contributors (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Table of Contents and note (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Text Copy: pp. 148-215 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Text Copy: pp. 216-283 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Text Copy: pp. 284-337 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Moore Correspondence: 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Introduction - Ellen G. Friedman and Miriam Fuchs (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - A Conversation with Kathy Acker - Ellen G. Friedman (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - On Violence - Kathy Acker (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Now Eat Your Mind: An Introduction to the Works of Kathy Acker - Ellen G. Fri~inan (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Now Eat Your Mind: An Introduction to the Works of Kathy Acker - Ellen G. Friedman (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Kathy Acker and the Plagiarized Self - Naomi Jacobs (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Kathy Acker' s Don Quixote: Nomad Writing -Douglas Shields Dix (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Confessions of a Kieptoparasite - Martina Sciolino (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Selective Menxry - Lynne Tiiman (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - A Sailor's Life in the Empire of the Senseless -Robert Siegle (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Works by Kathy Acker (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Conversation with Christine Brooke-Rose (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - From Verbivore - Christine Brooke-Rose (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - lilicitatioris - Christine Brooke-Rose (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - 'Just Words on a Page ':The Novels of Christine Brooks-Rose -Richard Martin (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Living Between, or, The Lon/veliness of the Alleinstehende Frau - Susan Robin Suleiman (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Thru the Looking Glass: A Journey into the Universe of Discourse - Hanjo Berressen (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Amalgamemnon and the Politics of Narrative - Judy Little (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - "Memory and Discourse: Fictionalizing the Present in Xorando - Susan E. Hawkins (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Works by Christine Brooke-Rose (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Conversation with Marguerite Young - Ellen G. Friedman and Miriam Fuchs (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - From Prelude in the Golden Key: The Life and Times of Eugene Victor Debs - Marguerite Young (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - On Teaching - Marguerite Young (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - "Marguenite Young's Utopias: 'The Most Beautiful Music [They] Had Never Heard - Miriam Fuchs (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Telling Women' s Time: Miss MacIntosh, My Denling -Susan Strehle (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Variations on Infinity: An Epic Elegy for All of Creation -Erika Duncan (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Miss MacIntosh, My Denling: Poetry of the Subconscious -Fatima Shaik (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Exorbitance and Death: Marguerite Young's Vision -Steven Shaviro (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Works by Marguerite Young (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Zuchs (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Table of Contents (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Text Copy: Corrected pages - Ellen G. Friedman (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Moore - McCourt (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Moore (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Moore - Creeley (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Once More unto the Breach, Dear Friends, Once More: The Publishing Scene and American Literary Art -George Garrett (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Postmodernism Revisited - Jobn Barth (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Postmodernism Revisited - Jobn Barth (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Writing and Writers: Disjecta Membra - Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Writing and Writers: Disjecta Membra - Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Fictional Futures and the Conspiciously Young -David Foster Wallace (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Fictional Futures and the Conspiciously Young -David Foster Wallace (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Conflictual Inscriptions - Claude Ollier (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Ill Locutions - Chnistine Brooke-Rose (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Ill Locutions - Chnistine Brooke-Rose (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Thinking of You - Robert Creeley (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Notes on the Threshold of a Book - Harry Mathews (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Notes on the Threshold of a Book - Harry Mathews (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Les Merveilleux Nuages - Harry Mathews (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Les Merveilleux Nuages - Harry Mathews (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Poundian Romance-Investigating Thomas McEviley's Novel, North of Yesterday -Robert Kelly (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Poundian Romance-Investigating Thomas McEviley's Novel, North of Yesterday - Robert Kelly (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Shadows and Marble: Richard Braritigan - Keith Abbott (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Inspector Javert' s Moment of Pure Aeschylus - Paul West (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Inspector Javert' s Moment of Pure Aeschylus - Paul West (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Strange Attraction: Exaltation and Calculation in the Poetry of James Schuyler - James MeCourt (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Reactionary - Thomas MaGonigle (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Afterword to Locos (or Felipe Alfau's Locos) Mary McCarthy (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Book Reviews (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Books Received pp. 173-178 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Contributors (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Text Copy: pp. 7-66 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Text Copy: pp. 67-116 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Text Copy: pp. 117-172 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Text Copy: miscellaneous pages (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Abbott (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Banks (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Clank (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Moore/Desenbrock - Jussawalla (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - DiBernardi (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Dukore (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Fleisher (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Garrett and Gifford (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Goytisolo (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Higgins (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Hunt (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Kernigan (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Kostelanetz (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Locklin (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Mccarthy (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: O 'Brian - McGonigle (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Markson (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Moore - Mathews (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Metcalf (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Metcalf 1981 - March 1988 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Moore, April - Oct. 1988 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Moore - O'Brien (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Moore (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Mosley (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Navarre (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Newlove (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Ollier (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Papeleo (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Polizzotti (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Rattroy (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Roth (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Schwerner and Lane (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Selby (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Simon (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Sorrentino, 1987 - 1989 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Sorrentino, 1988 - 1989, Restricted (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Stephens (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Sullivan (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien - Tindall (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Valenzuela (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brian - Waldrop (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: O'Brian - Wright (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Introduction - Jussawalla and Desenbrock (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Things That Appear - Zulfikar Ghose (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - From The Triple Mirror of the Self - Zulfikar Ghose (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Five Poems - Zulfikar Ghose (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - A Conversation with Zulfikar Ghose - Reed Way Desenbrock and Feroza Jussawalla (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - A Selection of Letters - Thomas Berger (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - From Fiction Complete - Serge Fauchereau (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - A Note on Zulfikar Ghose's 'Nature Strategies -Wison Harris (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Zulfflcar those and the Land of His Birth - Tariq Rahman (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - A Poetics of Location: Reading Zulfikar Ghose -Shirley Geok-lin Lim (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Structures of Uncertainty: Reading Ghosess 'The Zoo People -W. H. New (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - The Murder of Aziz Khan - Robert Ross (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Ghose's Criticism as Theory - Bruce King (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Fictional Self and Mythic Art: A New History of Tonnents and Don Bueno William J. Scheick (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Encountering the Other in The Fiction of Reality -Ewing Campbell (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - The Luminous Conprehension: From Realism to Counterrealism in the Writings of Zulfikar Ghose - C. Kanaganayakam (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Zulfikar those: A Selected Bibliography - C. Kanaganayakam (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Bibliography/Editing Notes (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Table of Contents (Zulfikar those issue) (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: O'Brien/Moore - Oppenheim (including some edited versions of drafts) (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Clarifications, Elucidations: An Interview with Milan Kundera - Lois Oppenbeim (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - On Criticism, Aesthetics, and Europe - Milan Kundera (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - The Fallen Idyll: A Rereading of Milan Kundera -Fromcois Ricard (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - On Kundera - Italo Calvino (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - The Impossible Don Juan: An Essay on Milan Kundera' S Laughable Loves - Maria Nemcova Banerjee (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Kundera and Jane Austen - John Bayley (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Eternal Return and The Unbearable Lightness of Being -Petra von Morstein (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Milan Kundera or the Hazards of Subjectivity -Bertrand Very (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - The Intrusive Narrative Voice of Milan Kundera -Ann Stewart Caldwell (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Jacques and His Master: Euxxlera and His Precursors -Ilan Stavans (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Selective Annotated Bibliography of Kundera Criticism -Glen Brand (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Books by Milan Kundera (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Book Reviews (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Books Received (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Contributors (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Table of Contents (Kundera issue) (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Corrected pages by Oppenheim (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Text Copy (Horrath's corrections): pp. 7-64 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Text Copy: pp. 65-106 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Text Copy: pp. 108-256 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Text Copy: pp. 108-237 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Reviewers cover letters etc.) (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Three Sketches - Maurice Roche (French with Enlish translation) (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Introduction (French issue) with Acknowledements (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - From Hortense is Abducted - Jacques Roubaud (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - On the Run from La Caverne Celeste - Patrick Grainville (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - The J~nce School from La Paradis des Orages -Patrick Grainville (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Radical Transformation from Lee Rois et les Voleurs -Muriel Cerf (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Far from God from Mordechai Schamz (Loin de Dieu II) -Marc Cholodenko (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Baby Drumn~nd from Romans, Un Roman - Wee Navarre (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - A Catholic Girlhood From Lee Arxroires Vides - Annie Ernaux (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Us These Pnotograpbs, No from Nous Ces Photoqraphies, Non -Mathieu Benezet (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - After Dark from Crepusculaires - Chantal Chawar (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Three Days of Don Juan - Rezvani (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - From Musical Auditions on Certain Surrnner Evening (Auditions Musicales Certains Soirs d' Ete) - Jeanne Hyvrard (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - '!Metaxnorphoses From Mentir - Eugene Savitzkaya (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Round and Round From La Ronde - J. M. G. La Clezio (sp?) (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Naja Naja From Voyages de 1 'autre cote - La Clezio (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Searching for Kaerner From Lee Portes de Gubbio (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - From Billy-ze-Kick - Jean Vautrin (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - From Monsieur Marellange ' s Score - Daniel Boulanger (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - The Flying Ace From Livret de Fainille - Patrick Modiano (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - French Novelists on Their Writing (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - French Issue - quicky evaluations (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - The collapse of the Great Balcony of the Occident or The Last Waltz - Yves Navarre (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - From Da Si Braves Garcons - Patrick Modiano (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - From L'Enlevement d'Hortense - Jacques Roubaud (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous (what is it?) (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Book Reviews (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Book Reviews: Spring (French) issue - 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Index - Books Reviewed (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Books Received (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Books Received (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Contributors (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Contributors (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Text Copy: pp. 7-69 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Text Copy: pp. 70-117 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Text copy: pp. 118-165 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Text Copy: pp. 166-215 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Text Copy: pp. 216-276 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Galleys (Book Reviewing in America) (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Text Copy: pp. 138-215 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Series II: Dalkey Archive Press
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence: Brotchie - Wright (Translators of Pierre Albert-Birot) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Stanley Crawford (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Liddy (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Beastmeat or the MacFaustus Festival Book - Jamss Liddy (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Beastmeat or the MacFaustus Festival Book - Jamss Liddy (pp. 42-81) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Beastmeat or the MacFaustus Festival Book - Jamss Liddy: (pp. 82-122) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Beastmeat or the MacFaustus Festival Book - Jamss Liddy: (pp.123-182) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: McGonigle 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: January 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: February 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: March-July 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous McGonigle Correspondence & Clippings #1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous McGonigle Correspondence & Clippings #2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous McGonigle Correspondence & Clippings #3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous McGonigle Correspondence & Clippings #4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous McGonigle Correspondence & Clippings #5 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - -Adrift #3 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - -Alone in Scandinavia - Thomas McGonigle (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - -Moments before Entering the Corn Exchange Thomas McGonig1e (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - -Down Here on Second Avenue Manhattan in 1983 Thomas McGonig1e (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Going to Patchoque - Thomas McGonigle (cover-p. 70) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Going to Patchoque - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 71-140) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Going to Patchoque - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 141-210) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Going to Patchoque - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 211-260) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Going to Patchoque - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 261-327) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle (cover-p. 60) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 61-120) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 121-188) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 14-84) Copy 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 85-145) Copy 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 146-206) Copy 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle: (pp. 207-266) Copy 2 (Includes correspondence concerning publication) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle Galley (title page-p. 70) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov - Thomas McGonigle Galley: (pp. 71-133) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Markson (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Corrections to Wittgenstein'sS Mistress (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson (Jacket Copy) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson: (title page-p.60) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson: (pp. 61-120) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson: (pp. 121-180) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson: (pp. 181-230) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress - Markson: (pp. 231-284) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Keeper of the Ghost - Markson (front matter-p. 61) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Keeper of the Ghost - Markson: (pp. 61-120) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Keeper of the Ghost - Markson: (pp. 121-180) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Keeper of the Ghost - Markson: (pp. 181-240) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Keeper of the Ghost - Markson: (pp. 241-285) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Mathews (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Singular Pleasures - Harry Mathews (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 20 Lines A Day - Harry Mathews (revisions) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews (pp. 4-70) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: (pp. 71-128) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: Mathews - copy of original (pp. 1-40) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: (pp. 41-80) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: (pp. 81-128 & notes) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: corrected galleys (pp. 3-45) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: (pp. 46-90) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews: (pp. 91-134) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 20 Lines - Harry Mathews (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Metcalf (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Metcalf (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - Metcalf (originals) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Book Reviews - Metcalf (originals) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Book Reviews - Metcalf (1) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Book Reviews - Metcalf (2) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses? - & corrections) copy 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 51-102) copy 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 103-165) copy 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 5-47) copy 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 48-102) copy 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 103-165) copy 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 31-102) copy 3 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: (pp. 103-165) copy 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Where Do You Put the Horses?: Final Copy (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Nicholas Mosley; "Afterword" - Steven Weisenberger (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Domke and DiBernardi (translators of Navarre) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre (corrected typescript: pp. 1-70) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 71-140) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 141-210) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 211-276) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (corrected galleys pp. 1-70) set I (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 71-140) set 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 141-187) set 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 188-237) set I (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 1-70) set 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 71-140) set 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 141-187) set 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre: (pp. 188-237) set 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Dominic DiBernardi (translator of Ollier) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected typescript: pp. 1-70) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected typescript: (pp. 71-140) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected typescript: (pp. 141-210) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected typescript: (pp. 211-280) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected typescriptL(pp.281-352) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (Afterward) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (Corrected galley pp.1-70) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier (corrected galley pp. 71-140) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Mise-en-Scene:(pp. 141-210) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Mise-en-Scene: (pp. 211-248 & Afterword) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Brotchie - Wright (translators of Queneau)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau (corrected typescript: pp. 1-70) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (pp. 71-138 & Afterword) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (corrected galley: transto' s preface-p. 70) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (pp. 71-159) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (corrected galley pp. 7-80) set 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (pp. 81-159) set 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Pierrot Mon Ami - Raymond Qeneau: (Jacket blurb) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Michael Stephens (Box 8, Folder 9)